maxthon.com 2012-11-30

# Privacy Policy | Maxthon

Maxthon (Asia) Ltd. (Maxthon) is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of its users. The purpose of this Maxthon privacy policy is to inform you of the types of information we may gather about you when you visit Maxthon.com, how we may use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to correct, the information. This privacy policy applies to Maxthon PC browsers, android browsers, websites, Maxthon Passport services, Maxthon SkyFile and 'Powered by Maxthon SkyFile' services.

This policy applies only to Maxthon, and not to other companies' or organizations' websites to which we link or to other products that may be distributed with the browser. You should carefully review the privacy policy of these other sites and products.

**Maxthon's Policy Towards Children**

Maxthon defines a child as someone under the age of 13 years. Our Services are not directed to persons under 13. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided Maxthon with Personal Information without their consent, he or she should contact us at [privacy@maxthon.com](mailto:privacy@maxthon.com). If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with Personal Information, we will take steps to delete such information from our files.

**Security**

Your security is important to Maxthon.Maxthon follows generally accepted standards to protect the information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) Maxthon encrypts the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). No method of electronic transmission or storage is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**Maxthon Community  **

Maxthon offers publicly accessible community services such as blogs, forums, and wikis. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. Your posts may remain even after you cancel your account.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

The following Privacy Policy may change to reflect compliance with new laws, new products and new technology. If Maxthon makes a change to this privacy policy we believe materially reduces your rights, we will provide you with notice (for example, by email). Maxthon may provide notice of changes in other circumstances as well. By continuing to use the Service after those changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy.

**Information Maxthon Collects and Stores**

We may collect and store the following types of information when running the Maxthon Applications and Services:

**Information Provided by You.**

When you register for a Maxthon Passport or SkyFile account Maxthon collects some personal information, such as your name, phone number, credit card or other billing information, email address and home and business postal addresses. You may also ask us to import your contacts by giving us access to your third party services (for example, your email account) or to use your social networking information if you give us access to your account on social network connection services.

Maxthon's desktop PC browser has the ability to gather certain information concerning your computer system but it will only send this information to Maxthon if you chose to send it. If you choose to provide feedback to us, this data will be sent to the Maxthon Browser team who will use the information for such purposes as diagnosing performance issues, improving the reliability of the download and install process, and improving its products and services to users generally. This feedback information from the browser is sandboxed and is not tied to any other information about you that you may have provided through another service.

During the installation process, or at some time thereafter, you may be asked to provide certain information that Maxthon will use to personalize content presented to you through the browser. For example, you may be asked for your Zip or postal code, which could be used by the browser to provide you with relevant local weather and/or news reports. The information gathered by the browser will not be tied to any information that would identify you personally. The websites you visit, including those of advertisers, have their own privacy policies. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of Web sites before providing them with any of your personal information.

**Files.  **

Maxthon SkyFile collects and stores the files you upload, download, or access with the SkyFile S (“my skyfile content”) and Passport services (“my notes.”) If you add a file to your skyfile content that has been previously uploaded by you or another user, we may associate all or a portion of the previous file with your account rather than storing a duplicate.

**Server Log Data.  **

When you use the Service, Maxthon automatically record information from your Device, its software, and your activity using the Services. This may include the Device’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, the web page visited before you came to our website, information you search for on our website, locale preferences, identification numbers associated with your Devices, your mobile carrier, date and time stamps associated with transactions, system configuration information, metadata concerning your Files, and other interactions with the Service.

**Cookies.  **

Maxthon uses “cookies” to collect information and improve our Services. A cookie is a small data file that a Maxthon application or service transfers to your Device. We may use “persistent cookies” to save your registration ID and login password for future logins to our Services. We may use “session ID cookies” to enable certain features of the Service, to better understand how you interact with the Service and to monitor aggregate usage and web traffic routing on the Service. You can instruct your browser, by changing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all aspects of the Service.

##  How Maxthon Uses Personal Information

**Personal Information**

In the course of using the Service, Maxthon may collect personal information that can be used to contact or identify you (“Personal Information”). Personal Information is or may be used: (i) to provide and improve our Service, (ii) to administer your use of the Service, (iii) to better understand your needs and interests, (iv) to personalize and improve your experience, and (v) to provide or offer software updates and product announcements. If you no longer wish to receive communications from us, please follow the “unsubscribe” instructions provided in any of those communications, or update youraccount settings information.

**Geo-Location Information**

Some Devices allow applications to access real-time location-based information (for example, GPS). Our mobile apps do not collect such information as of the date this policy went into effect, but may do so in the future with your consent to improve our Services. Some photos you place in Maxthon SkyFile may contain recorded location information. We may use this information to optimize your experience. Also, some of the information we collect from a Device, for example IP address, can sometimes be used to approximate a Device’s location.

**Analytics**

Maxthon collects some information (ourselves or using third party services) using logging and cookies, which can sometimes be correlated with Personal Information. We use this information for the above purposes and to monitor and analyze use of the Service, for the Service’s technical administration, to increase our Service’s functionality and ease of use, and to verify users have the authorization needed for the Service to process their requests. As of the date this policy went into effect, Maxthon uses Google Analytics.

##  Information Sharing and Disclosure

**Your Use**  
We will display your Personal Information in your profile page and elsewhere on our Services according to the preferences you set in your account. Any information you choose to provide should reflect how much you want others to know about you. Please consider carefully what information you disclose in your profile page and your desired level of anonymity. You can review and revise your profile information at any time. We may also share or disclose your information with your consent, for example if you use a third party application to access your account (see below). Through certain features of the Services, you may also have the ability to make some of your information public. Public information may be broadly and quickly disseminated.

**Service Providers, Business Partners and Others  **

We may use certain trusted third party companies and individuals to help us provide, analyze, and improve the Service (including but not limited to data storage, maintenance services, database management, web analytics, payment processing, and improvement of the Service’s features). These third parties may have access to your information only for purposes of performing these tasks on our behalf and under obligations similar to those in this Privacy Policy. As of the date this policy went into effect, we use Amazon’s S3 storage service to store some of your information and PayPal payment processing.

**Third-Party Applications  **

We may share your information with a third party application with your consent, for example when you choose to access our Services through such an application. We are not responsible for what those parties do with your information, so you should make sure you trust the application and that it has a privacy policy acceptable to you.

**Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement Requests; Protection of Maxthon's Rights**

We may disclose to parties outside Maxthon files stored in your My SkyFile folder and information about you that we collect when we have a good faith belief that disclosure is reasonably necessary to (a) comply with a law, regulation or compulsory legal request; (b) protect the safety of any person from death or serious bodily injury; (c) prevent fraud or abuse of Maxthon services or its users; or (d) to protect Maxthon’s property rights. If we provide your SkyFile files to a law enforcement agency as set forth above, we will remove any Maxthon-provided encryption from the files before providing them to law enforcement. Maxthon will not be able to decrypt any files that you encrypted prior to storing them with SkyFile.

**Business Transfers  **

If we are involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, your information may be transferred as part of that transaction, but we will notify you (for example, via email and/or a prominent notice on our website) of any change in control or use of your Personal Information or Files, or if either become subject to a different Privacy Policy. We will also notify you of choices you may have regarding the information.

**Non-private or Non-Personal Information**

We may disclose your non-private, aggregated, or otherwise non-personal information, such as usage statistics of our Service.

**Changing or Deleting Your Information**

If you are a registered user, you may review, update, correct or delete the Personal Information provided in your registration or account profile by changing your “account settings.” If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may update or delete it by making the change on your account settings. In some cases we may retain copies of your information if required by law.

**Data Retention**

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services, you may delete your account. We may retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. We will try to delete your information quickly upon request. Please note, however, that there might be latency in deleting information from our servers and backed-up versions might exist after deletion. In addition, we do not delete from our servers files that you have in common with other users.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

The following Privacy Policy may change to reflect compliance with new laws, new products and new technology. If Maxthon makes a change to this privacy policy we believe materially reduces your rights, we will provide you with notice (for example, by email). Maxthon may provide notice of changes in other circumstances as well. By continuing to use the Service after those changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy.

**Disclosure**

We do not use or disclose information about your individual visits to Maxthon or information that you may give us on Maxthon, such as your name, address, email address or telephone number, to any outside companies or governmental agencies. Maxthon may share such information in response to legal process, such as a court order or subpoena. And, as we mention above, we may share with our website partners aggregated statistical information about the use of Maxthon.

**Contacting Maxthon**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [privacy@maxthon.com](mailto:privacy@maxthon.com).
